I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
Magnificent... It's like I have yet
to glimpse the end of your potential.
Likewise.
Show me everything.
There is one thing I can say for certain.
The one advantage I have when facing you...
is my greater variety of options.
This damned pig has gotten harder again.
Episode 21: The Moon and Tonkatsu
Hey! Quit outshining me!
Now's not the time!
Stay focused.
He's going to regenerate again.
Damn it! Which part will
it be from this time?
Let's go over what we know...
I'd rather not.
First, this pig is immortal.
You can cut its head off, crush its heart,
but it will regenerate
from some random piece.
And every time, it gets stronger.
I said I didn't wanna hear it!
At first, a single blow from Rozelis
was enough to take its head off.
But now it takes all three
of us, working together...
The more it dies, the stronger it gets?
I Was Reincarnated as an Edible Orc so I
Can Take My Time Annihilating Humanity.
I Was Reincarnated as an Edible Orc
so I Can Take My Time Annihilating Humanity
No, no, no!
The Pope's Forces SSS-Rank Chimera
Mega Meat
I'm not really sure what my deal is.
Even my master doesn't seem to understand.
This chimera wasn't made by the Pope?
And that's none of your business anyway.
Pork Punch!
Here we go again...
Die.
Babylon!
Before you kill me, I need to know...
Why do you hate humans so much?
I want to know your reasoning.
You're that interested in my history?
Sure! Tell us all about it!
No, not really—
We're bishops. It's part of our job to
offer righteous guidance to lost lambs.
Suit yourselves.
Let's see if you can guide me...
It all started a few years ago.
I was created by a certain alchemist.
At long last!
I, the brilliant Ouroboro's
greatest work is completed!
A source of infinite pork,
no matter how much you eat!
Ouroboro Number 6!
Time for a taste test!
Incredible! I cut and I cut and
it just grows back! Huge success!
Not only that, but the main
body seems to have grown, too!
You're going to save people
across the world from famine...
We'll rename you Mega Meat,
as you begin your ascent to fame!
Ba-dump...
I was happy.
Happy about being able to
help people, with my body.
And that my creator was so happy...
Oh, hell no! That's not edible at all!
Until that moment!
Number 6!
After that, I went around
feeding my flesh to humans.
But they all puked...
and after the hundredth spew,
around that time people were spreading
rumors of the monstrous pig man...
That's when I realized something.
I tasted bad!
You people could never understand...
I was born to be eaten,
but tasted so incredibly bad
that even flies would turn away...
And as I was sinking into despair,
I encountered my master.
Chomp
Magnificent.
Ba-dump...
I can feel your flesh's potential
for infinite regeneration.
Yet at the same time,
it does have an odd taste.
Your power should not be
used for the sake of man.
It is a weapon, that should be used against
the people who treated you like livestock...
Do you really intend on
letting their egotistic aims
sully the proud, rich,
monstrous bloodlines you embody?
He had a point.
And when he pointed it out,
I was pissed off.
I can't think of anything to say to him...
I'm going to take vengeance
on all of humanity, who has
the nerve to say I taste bad!
I Switched Jobs and Found My Guild Was in Dire Straights so Now I'm Really in Trouble!
I Switched Jobs and Found My Guild Was
in Dire Straights so Now I'm Really in Trouble!!
Knock it off!
Stop making this conversation
even more absurd!
Sorry
Doesn't
talk
Poisonous
Keeps adopting
new friends
Big
eater
Drunk
The Lovable Scamps
Back in the day, it felt like I was
living on the edge all the time...
I'd wander the woods in search of food,
Is this edible?
Stretching what little money we
had as far as it would go...
Searching everywhere I could for a
job to earn us some money for food.
Better eat the skin...
If I had met you back then,
I probably would've taken you into my arms.
Ba-dump...
D-Don't be stupid!
You're only saying that because
you don't know how nasty I taste!
I'll make you into the kind of pork
dish the entire world will love!
Ba-doink
What exactly is going on here?
The world's turned monochrome from
how little hope I have left.
Thinking's a dead end, Rozelis.
If we can't beat our opponent physically,
the only choice is to cook him up
tastily so he'll change his ways!
Hang on, Thor... you say that, but...
How is it possible to cook food with
that purple aura into anything tasty?!
We need to save his soul
so we need to eat with all we've got!
So we're stuck as the taste testers?!
I don't know what you think you're doing,
but you'll see soon enough
just how terrifying my
uncookable meat is!
Dink
Did you hear that dink?!
That meat's not frozen, is it?!
It's freshly cut, isn't it?!
Quit freaking out!
You're making me scared, too!
That's right. Before anything
else, my meat is hard.
What could a cook with
your skills possibly do?
Relax. I already know how to
deal with this tough slab.
What?!
You can't beat it tender.
You need the opposite approach, in fact.
Gently stroke it...
Stroke
What are you doing?! There's no way
you can soften meat like that!
No, look!
Flop...
The meat's gone downright
floppy, it's so soft!
How?!
You evolved in a way where, the more you're
killed, the harder your flesh became.
I figured the trick would be
to get that flesh to regress.
Sorry for attacking you so senselessly.
But it's okay now. You can relax.
Impossible!
Did that slab really give in?
Am I really that easy?!
Well, as much as I'd like to praise you
for getting past how tough my meat is...
What are you doing now, Babylon?
There's more to how unappetizing I am.
Specifically, how gamy it is.
There was one chef who tried
to get rid of the aroma...
The resulting smell was bad enough
to shutter his restaurant!
There's no seasoning or chef capable...
of overcoming it!
Pork...
I think... I'll call this dish... Tonkatsu.
Well I don't-katsu think you'll win!
As much as I hate to admit it...
It looks so crispy, fried, and delicious...
Downright colorful.
Let's see you eat it then!
And if you're able to
choke it down without puking,
I'll reconsider my revenge on mankind.
Listen up, just swallow
it without chewing much.
It's pointless. I bet you think that
batter will conceal the gaminess.
But it's going to have the opposite affect.
Once the crust is cracked open,
the aroma will burst forth,
Let's go on three.
On three, then...
and once you're caught in it,
you'll be barfing up a storm!
Chew.
I can't stop chewing it!
What a delightful texture!
We're bishops, yet we're possessed with
an inter-mouth impulse for destruction!
And it leaves the mischievous priests we've
been turned into with only one option...
Look! Let's go swimming!
to dive in!
Into this overflowing stream
of savory juiciness!
Delicious!
Impossible! There's no way that's true!
But it really is!
It's like every bite spurs
more flavor out of the meat!
What the hell did you do?
During the prep stage...
I added a handful of Glow.
Fresh...
What a delicious-looking
cut of pork sirloin!
It's said that advanced enough purification
can turn gutter water pristine...
Babylon! Your divine sorcery is brilliant!
I definitely wouldn't call it brilliant.
I only shone the faintest
bit of light on it.
Which made it clear...
Mega Meat, you're a good guy.
You dedicated your existence to others,
while beset on all sides by despair...
That's where that nasty taste stems from.
But my Glow was enough to
wash it away, with ease.
That shows the kind of softy you are...
Mommy, something smells good!
You should live how you want to, Mega Meat.
Who would be cooking at a time
like this, instead of evacuating?
But never forget...
Delicious!
...humans love you.
It doesn't matter how mad I get...
Whenever I see this sight,
I just have to let it go.
Thank you for the food!
Be sure to take some to the shelter!
This meat really is incredible!
Once I start selling
Rozelis-branded Mega Meat,
I'll have solved famines around the
globe, and won hordes of converts!
That settles it!
Let me take care of this pig—
Babylon was your name, right?
I want you to purify me.
Hang on, Mega Meat!
I get the feeling your regeneration
is tied to your anger and hatred.
Purify that, and you might
just be an ordinary pig!
It'd be such a waste...
I know.
I will no longer be infinite.
It might reduce me to a single serving.
But I want to be eaten, at my tastiest...
by you, Babylon.
Forgive me, Master.
Professor Ouroboro.
But I want to live for the sake of others!
I won't be saving everyone
in the world from hunger...
The gaminess... is going away...
The flavor!
But I'll be going into the stomach of
the only person to ever understand me!
I...
I guess that's it.
I made a promise after all...
Damn it! There's no way I can eat you!
Mega Meat (The Endless No. 6)
Joined the party.
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
It's really quite impressive.
Luxa should be more than capable of
slicing through that candelabra...
But in your hands,
that seems to not be the case.
Almost like sorcery.
I'm only asking to confirm...
You're not also the mysterious
pastor, are you?
The mysterious pastor? Oh, not at all.
My master stands at heights
far beyond my reach.
Despite being a bishop,
your swordplay lives up to its reputation.
I can't deny being curious about this
master of which you speak so highly.
Your reputation precedes you
as well, Silver Blader.
Something about leaving the field as soon
as you became an A-Rank adventurer.
Why choose to become a maid, instead?
You don't have to answer if you don't—
Because I met...
someone I was fated to stand beside.
Well, that was certainly
not the answer I expected.
It seems as if neither
of us can lose, then...
For the sake of those we serve.
Luxa: Lunar Spectrum.
Rainbow-colored smoke?!
Midnight Sun.
Fickle Fog!
And a circle of rainbow-colored giants?
No. Don't fall for it.
This is just that phenomenon
seen at high altitudes,
an interaction of light and shadow.
In other words, it's no threat!
That wasn't a shadow.
Then is all of this mist her Luxa?!
There're too many strikes aimed at me.
It's not giving me time to focus on defense,
and the candelabra isn't
going to last much longer.
Anastasia won't leave any openings.
Flop...
She's dead set on waiting until both
my weapon and I are worn down.
But that will be when she exposes herself.
It'll be settled in an instant!
The Silver Blader.
So proud, and beautiful,
in service to her master...
Such a splendid servant.
As another dedicated to service,
you are too brilliant for my eyes.
I... am ugly, and foul.
We're gonna get something good to eat.
I drove my master mad.
Anastasia...
I don't resent you.
If you want to turn back,
this is your chance.
That time has long passed.
Master Guitane... I will remain by your side,
even if that's not what you want.
I can hear
how that candelabra in your hands is barely
able to function as a metal stick anymore.
I'll at least do you the honor
of ending your life myself.
Draconic Moon-Eater!
Why didn't you kill me?
That Luxa... you altered
it to have a blunt edge.
I had no idea... that you
could use divine sorcery.
It was a gift from my master.
What's this glass ball?
It's got the mana signature for Luxa on it!
Just squeeze it and channel your mana,
and it should take the shape
of a Luxa to your liking.
As happy as this makes me,
I-I'm not very confident with mana...
I had intended to bring a sword with me...
There's a chance the church might
confiscate any weapons you try to bring.
Lloyd!
Let's practice singing!
Well, if you don't end up
needing it, all the better.
P-Prince Lloyd!
Thank you so much.
My master is wise, impressive, and cute...
But still makes such blunders at times,
and makes the most incredible
faces when I scold him...
He has no shortage of secrets.
That said, I'm prepared to wait until
he's ready to share them with me.
Mana depletion? I really don't
have much at all, do I?
To be this exhausted from
summoning a single sword...
I...
would never dream... of scolding mine.
Even though... that may
be what he longs for.
For someone to stop him...
But...
it can't be me.
My voice can't reach him.
Like the sky on a rainy night...
A cold abyss without a point of starlight...
that's what his heart has become.
Ever since... that day.
All I can manage...
is to serve as a hazy moon.
As a simple maid, I'm in no
position to judge either of you.
I hope he hears it, though.
Maybe by the end of this battle...
someone's voice...
will reach your master.
Sadly, defeating me will not prevent the
kingdom from being swallowed by the darkness.
Next time, on episode 22:
Episode 22
Black Dragon
"Black Dragon."
You will witness the depths of sorcery.